BABITA BISHT

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-motivated Software Developer with experience of 4 yrs. Have experience in working different scales and types of technologies and industries. Exuberant to learn new technologies and solve real world problems . I am looking for opportunities that will help me grow as a professionally as well as personally.

CONTACT

- 7895405902
- babitabisht179@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/babita-bisht-9391281b7/
- https://www.github.com/babita971
- ★ Hinjewadi, Pune

EDUCATION

BTKIT Dwarahat, Uttarakhand

Bachelor of Technology - Computer Science Engineering

July 2014 - May 2018 (GPA - 3/4)

Kendriya Vidyalaya Pithoragarh

AISSCE - PCM (2012-2013) - 85%

Kendriya Vidyalaya Pithoragarh

SSC (2010-2011) - 87%

SKILLS

- Mobile application development using Flutter and GetX. Front-end and back-end web development with LAMP stack.
- Code structure and architecture
- Programming languages- Dart, SQL, JS, HTML5,
 CSS3 and Core Java.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Antares Tech | Noida | WFH

Mobile Application Developer

May 2022 - Mar 2023

 Worked as a flutter developer for a fintech company in Bangalore.

Tezminds Software | Pune | WFH

Software Developer

Jan 2021 - Apr 2022

- Worked as a front-end developer using HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery and Bootstrap and back-end developer using with LAMP stack, MySql and MongoDB.
- Was responsible for creating new pages and REST apis from scratch for web applications.
- Also worked with flutter to create android app for cattle feed company.

Accenture | Pune | WFO

Associate Software Engineer

Nov 2018- Aug 2020

Worked as a SAP BW-BODS consultant.
 Experienced in ETL processes, monitoring, data modelling and creating reports using Power BI and Data analysis in SAP Analyzer.

PERSONAL HOBBIES

Music, Painting, Documentaries and Walking.